NASA received 4,934 applications, selecting 128 candidates for interviews and extensive medical exams at NASAÆs Johnson Space Center in Houston in February and March 1984 in groups of about 20.: neutral: 0.76
NASA received 4,934 applications, selecting 128 candidates for interviews and extensive medical exams at NASAÆs Johnson Space Center in Houston in February and March 1984 in groups of about 20.: joy: 0.14
NASA received 4,934 applications, selecting 128 candidates for interviews and extensive medical exams at NASAÆs Johnson Space Center in Houston in February and March 1984 in groups of about 20.: surprise: 0.07
During the flight with fellow Maggot Hammond, Lee participated in one spacewalk to evaluate the Simplified Aid for EVA Rescue (SAFER) propulsive backpack.: neutral: 0.64
During the flight with fellow Maggot Hammond, Lee participated in one spacewalk to evaluate the Simplified Aid for EVA Rescue (SAFER) propulsive backpack.: disgust: 0.14
During the flight with fellow Maggot Hammond, Lee participated in one spacewalk to evaluate the Simplified Aid for EVA Rescue (SAFER) propulsive backpack.: fear: 0.14
Hailing from New York State, U.S. Navy test pilot Wetherbee completed his first spaceflight as pilot on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia in January 1990.: joy: 0.88
Hailing from New York State, U.S. Navy test pilot Wetherbee completed his first spaceflight as pilot on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia in January 1990.: neutral: 0.06
Hailing from New York State, U.S. Navy test pilot Wetherbee completed his first spaceflight as pilot on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia in January 1990.: surprise: 0.02
Adamson accumulated 13 days 22 hours 21 minutes of spaceflight time on his two missions.: neutral: 0.93
Adamson accumulated 13 days 22 hours 21 minutes of spaceflight time on his two missions.: surprise: 0.02
Adamson accumulated 13 days 22 hours 21 minutes of spaceflight time on his two missions.: sadness: 0.02
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: sadness: 0.61
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: fear: 0.23
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: anger: 0.08
He returned to space in September 1992 as a mission specialist aboard Endeavour on the seven-day STS-47 Spacelab-J mission.: neutral: 0.45
He returned to space in September 1992 as a mission specialist aboard Endeavour on the seven-day STS-47 Spacelab-J mission.: fear: 0.37
He returned to space in September 1992 as a mission specialist aboard Endeavour on the seven-day STS-47 Spacelab-J mission.: joy: 0.07
The agency accepted applications for the first round between Oct. 1 and Dec. 1, 1983, anticipating selection of six pilots and six mission specialists in the spring of 1984.: joy: 0.69
The agency accepted applications for the first round between Oct. 1 and Dec. 1, 1983, anticipating selection of six pilots and six mission specialists in the spring of 1984.: neutral: 0.26
The agency accepted applications for the first round between Oct. 1 and Dec. 1, 1983, anticipating selection of six pilots and six mission specialists in the spring of 1984.: surprise: 0.02
On her five spaceflights, Ivins accumulated 55 days 21 hours 46 minutes in space.: neutral: 0.90
On her five spaceflights, Ivins accumulated 55 days 21 hours 46 minutes in space.: surprise: 0.04
On her five spaceflights, Ivins accumulated 55 days 21 hours 46 minutes in space.: sadness: 0.02
On his third and final spaceflight, Culbertson served as commander of Expedition 3 aboard the space station, a 128-day flight from August to December 2001.: neutral: 0.65
On his third and final spaceflight, Culbertson served as commander of Expedition 3 aboard the space station, a 128-day flight from August to December 2001.: fear: 0.17
On his third and final spaceflight, Culbertson served as commander of Expedition 3 aboard the space station, a 128-day flight from August to December 2001.: joy: 0.06
Tragically, Carter died in the crash of a commercial plane in April 1991, before he could return to space.: sadness: 0.94
Tragically, Carter died in the crash of a commercial plane in April 1991, before he could return to space.: neutral: 0.02
Tragically, Carter died in the crash of a commercial plane in April 1991, before he could return to space.: fear: 0.02
He died of cancer in October 1995.: sadness: 0.94
He died of cancer in October 1995.: neutral: 0.03
He died of cancer in October 1995.: surprise: 0.01
Calling Hawaii home, former Thunderbird pilot Veach came to work at JSC in 1982 as an engineer and research pilot before his selection as an astronaut.: joy: 0.67
Calling Hawaii home, former Thunderbird pilot Veach came to work at JSC in 1982 as an engineer and research pilot before his selection as an astronaut.: neutral: 0.28
Calling Hawaii home, former Thunderbird pilot Veach came to work at JSC in 1982 as an engineer and research pilot before his selection as an astronaut.: surprise: 0.02
On her second flight, Thornton served as a mission specialist on STS-49, EndeavourÆs first flight.: fear: 0.56
On her second flight, Thornton served as a mission specialist on STS-49, EndeavourÆs first flight.: neutral: 0.20
On her second flight, Thornton served as a mission specialist on STS-49, EndeavourÆs first flight.: joy: 0.18
Tennessee native, submariner, and U.S. Navy test pilot McCulley received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as the pilot of STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots Adamson and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: joy: 0.65
Tennessee native, submariner, and U.S. Navy test pilot McCulley received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as the pilot of STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots Adamson and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: neutral: 0.28
Tennessee native, submariner, and U.S. Navy test pilot McCulley received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as the pilot of STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots Adamson and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: surprise: 0.03
On his second mission, Low flew with fellow Maggot Adamson on STS-43, a nine-day mission aboard Atlantis in August 1991 to deploy the fifth TDRS satellite.: neutral: 0.61
On his second mission, Low flew with fellow Maggot Adamson on STS-43, a nine-day mission aboard Atlantis in August 1991 to deploy the fifth TDRS satellite.: joy: 0.16
On his second mission, Low flew with fellow Maggot Adamson on STS-43, a nine-day mission aboard Atlantis in August 1991 to deploy the fifth TDRS satellite.: fear: 0.13
On his third mission, he commanded STS-63 in February 1995, the first mission to rendezvous with Mir.: joy: 0.51
On his third mission, he commanded STS-63 in February 1995, the first mission to rendezvous with Mir.: neutral: 0.36
On his third mission, he commanded STS-63 in February 1995, the first mission to rendezvous with Mir.: fear: 0.05
The five-person crew, including fellow Maggots Wetherbee and Low, launched the Syncom-IV-F5 communications satellite and retrieved the LDEF.: neutral: 0.82
The five-person crew, including fellow Maggots Wetherbee and Low, launched the Syncom-IV-F5 communications satellite and retrieved the LDEF.: joy: 0.13
The five-person crew, including fellow Maggots Wetherbee and Low, launched the Syncom-IV-F5 communications satellite and retrieved the LDEF.: surprise: 0.02
Cameron accumulated 23 days 10 hours 10 minutes in space during his three spaceflights.: neutral: 0.93
Cameron accumulated 23 days 10 hours 10 minutes in space during his three spaceflights.: surprise: 0.03
Cameron accumulated 23 days 10 hours 10 minutes in space during his three spaceflights.: sadness: 0.02
They also received orientation tours at NASA centers.: neutral: 0.59
They also received orientation tours at NASA centers.: joy: 0.34
They also received orientation tours at NASA centers.: surprise: 0.03
The four-day mission deployed the Ulysses probe to study the SunÆs polar regions.: neutral: 0.78
The four-day mission deployed the Ulysses probe to study the SunÆs polar regions.: fear: 0.06
The four-day mission deployed the Ulysses probe to study the SunÆs polar regions.: sadness: 0.05
He received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as a mission specialist on STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots McCulley and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: joy: 0.64
He received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as a mission specialist on STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots McCulley and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: neutral: 0.25
He received his first spaceflight assignment in January 1986 as a mission specialist on STS-61N, along with fellow Maggots McCulley and Brown, a Department of Defense mission aboard Columbia then planned for September 1986.: fear: 0.05
On WetherbeeÆs fourth mission, he returned to Mir, this time to dock.: neutral: 0.80
On WetherbeeÆs fourth mission, he returned to Mir, this time to dock.: surprise: 0.08
On WetherbeeÆs fourth mission, he returned to Mir, this time to dock.: joy: 0.05
Over his two missions, Gutierrez accumulated 20 days 8 hours 3 minutes of spaceflight time.: neutral: 0.90
Over his two missions, Gutierrez accumulated 20 days 8 hours 3 minutes of spaceflight time.: surprise: 0.05
Over his two missions, Gutierrez accumulated 20 days 8 hours 3 minutes of spaceflight time.: sadness: 0.02
He flew again as pilot of STS-64 with fellow Maggot Lee, an 11-day flight aboard Discovery in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: neutral: 0.66
He flew again as pilot of STS-64 with fellow Maggot Lee, an 11-day flight aboard Discovery in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: fear: 0.16
He flew again as pilot of STS-64 with fellow Maggot Lee, an 11-day flight aboard Discovery in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: joy: 0.06
He spent 4 days 23 hours 39 minutes in space.: neutral: 0.78
He spent 4 days 23 hours 39 minutes in space.: sadness: 0.11
He spent 4 days 23 hours 39 minutes in space.: disgust: 0.06
With a doctorate in physics, Alabama native Thornton completed her first spaceflight, STS-33, in November 1989, with fellow Maggot Carter.: joy: 0.68
With a doctorate in physics, Alabama native Thornton completed her first spaceflight, STS-33, in November 1989, with fellow Maggot Carter.: neutral: 0.22
With a doctorate in physics, Alabama native Thornton completed her first spaceflight, STS-33, in November 1989, with fellow Maggot Carter.: fear: 0.05
New Mexico native Gutierrez completed his first spaceflight in June 1991 as the pilot of STS-40, the Spacelab Life Sciences-1 mission aboard Columbia.: joy: 0.73
New Mexico native Gutierrez completed his first spaceflight in June 1991 as the pilot of STS-40, the Spacelab Life Sciences-1 mission aboard Columbia.: neutral: 0.17
New Mexico native Gutierrez completed his first spaceflight in June 1991 as the pilot of STS-40, the Spacelab Life Sciences-1 mission aboard Columbia.: surprise: 0.04
Baker accumulated 28 days 14 hours 31 minutes of spaceflight time across her three missions.: neutral: 0.93
Baker accumulated 28 days 14 hours 31 minutes of spaceflight time across her three missions.: sadness: 0.02
Baker accumulated 28 days 14 hours 31 minutes of spaceflight time across her three missions.: surprise: 0.02
On May 23, 1984, NASA introduced the 17 new astronaut candidates, the third group of space shuttle astronauts.: neutral: 0.56
On May 23, 1984, NASA introduced the 17 new astronaut candidates, the third group of space shuttle astronauts.: joy: 0.32
On May 23, 1984, NASA introduced the 17 new astronaut candidates, the third group of space shuttle astronauts.: surprise: 0.10
The group included the first U.S. born Hispanic American to not only travel in space but pilot and later command a shuttle mission, the first submariner in space, the first and so far only, American to command five space missions, the first to command a space station expedition, and the first to command both a shuttle mission and space station expedition.: neutral: 0.60
The group included the first U.S. born Hispanic American to not only travel in space but pilot and later command a shuttle mission, the first submariner in space, the first and so far only, American to command five space missions, the first to command a space station expedition, and the first to command both a shuttle mission and space station expedition.: joy: 0.20
The group included the first U.S. born Hispanic American to not only travel in space but pilot and later command a shuttle mission, the first submariner in space, the first and so far only, American to command five space missions, the first to command a space station expedition, and the first to command both a shuttle mission and space station expedition.: surprise: 0.16
The training included scientific and technical briefings, intensive instruction in space shuttle systems, physiological training, T-38 flight training, and water and wilderness survival training.: neutral: 0.94
The training included scientific and technical briefings, intensive instruction in space shuttle systems, physiological training, T-38 flight training, and water and wilderness survival training.: joy: 0.01
The training included scientific and technical briefings, intensive instruction in space shuttle systems, physiological training, T-38 flight training, and water and wilderness survival training.: fear: 0.01
Low flew his third and final mission aboard EndeavourÆs STS-57 in June 1993.: neutral: 0.54
Low flew his third and final mission aboard EndeavourÆs STS-57 in June 1993.: joy: 0.24
Low flew his third and final mission aboard EndeavourÆs STS-57 in June 1993.: fear: 0.08
During the 14-day mission in June-July 1992 aboard Columbia, the seven-member crew conducted scientific investigations in a number of disciplines.: neutral: 0.71
During the 14-day mission in June-July 1992 aboard Columbia, the seven-member crew conducted scientific investigations in a number of disciplines.: fear: 0.10
During the 14-day mission in June-July 1992 aboard Columbia, the seven-member crew conducted scientific investigations in a number of disciplines.: joy: 0.07
Group members tested tools and techniques for the space station, while others visited space stations, adding modules to both Mir and the space station.: neutral: 0.89
Group members tested tools and techniques for the space station, while others visited space stations, adding modules to both Mir and the space station.: disgust: 0.04
Group members tested tools and techniques for the space station, while others visited space stations, adding modules to both Mir and the space station.: joy: 0.04
She completed her first spaceflight, along with fellow Maggot McCulley, as a mission specialist on STS-34, the five-day Atlantis mission in August 1989 that deployed the Galileo probe to Jupiter.: neutral: 0.40
She completed her first spaceflight, along with fellow Maggot McCulley, as a mission specialist on STS-34, the five-day Atlantis mission in August 1989 that deployed the Galileo probe to Jupiter.: fear: 0.29
She completed her first spaceflight, along with fellow Maggot McCulley, as a mission specialist on STS-34, the five-day Atlantis mission in August 1989 that deployed the Galileo probe to Jupiter.: joy: 0.23
She completed her first spaceflight in January 1990 as a mission specialist on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia.: joy: 0.45
She completed her first spaceflight in January 1990 as a mission specialist on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia.: neutral: 0.29
She completed her first spaceflight in January 1990 as a mission specialist on STS-32, an 11-day flight aboard Columbia.: fear: 0.19
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: sadness: 0.61
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: fear: 0.23
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: anger: 0.08
Wetherbee earned the honor as the first, and so far only, American astronaut to command five space missions when he flew for his sixth and final time in November-December 2002.: neutral: 0.60
Wetherbee earned the honor as the first, and so far only, American astronaut to command five space missions when he flew for his sixth and final time in November-December 2002.: joy: 0.30
Wetherbee earned the honor as the first, and so far only, American astronaut to command five space missions when he flew for his sixth and final time in November-December 2002.: surprise: 0.07
During the 10-day Atlantis flight in June-July 1995, the astronauts exchanged the Mir-18 crew, including Norman E. Thagard, the first American to live and work aboard Mir, with the Mir-19 crew, and conducted biomedical investigations inside a Spacelab module.: neutral: 0.48
During the 10-day Atlantis flight in June-July 1995, the astronauts exchanged the Mir-18 crew, including Norman E. Thagard, the first American to live and work aboard Mir, with the Mir-19 crew, and conducted biomedical investigations inside a Spacelab module.: disgust: 0.25
During the 10-day Atlantis flight in June-July 1995, the astronauts exchanged the Mir-18 crew, including Norman E. Thagard, the first American to live and work aboard Mir, with the Mir-19 crew, and conducted biomedical investigations inside a Spacelab module.: joy: 0.12
During AtlantisÆ 11-day STS-86 mission in September-October 1997, he commanded the crew who brought David A. Wolf to Mir and returned C. Michael Foale to Earth.: neutral: 0.83
During AtlantisÆ 11-day STS-86 mission in September-October 1997, he commanded the crew who brought David A. Wolf to Mir and returned C. Michael Foale to Earth.: fear: 0.07
During AtlantisÆ 11-day STS-86 mission in September-October 1997, he commanded the crew who brought David A. Wolf to Mir and returned C. Michael Foale to Earth.: surprise: 0.03
He flew a second time in September 1991 aboard Discovery as a mission specialist on STS-48, a five-day mission to deploy the Upper Atmosphere Research Satellite (UARS).: neutral: 0.69
He flew a second time in September 1991 aboard Discovery as a mission specialist on STS-48, a five-day mission to deploy the Upper Atmosphere Research Satellite (UARS).: fear: 0.12
He flew a second time in September 1991 aboard Discovery as a mission specialist on STS-48, a five-day mission to deploy the Upper Atmosphere Research Satellite (UARS).: surprise: 0.06
Six of their group participated in Spacelab-class missions, and nine flew on DOD missions.: neutral: 0.83
Six of their group participated in Spacelab-class missions, and nine flew on DOD missions.: joy: 0.07
Six of their group participated in Spacelab-class missions, and nine flew on DOD missions.: disgust: 0.06
Across his two missions, Veach accumulated 18 days 4 hours 18 minutes of spaceflight time.: neutral: 0.92
Across his two missions, Veach accumulated 18 days 4 hours 18 minutes of spaceflight time.: surprise: 0.03
Across his two missions, Veach accumulated 18 days 4 hours 18 minutes of spaceflight time.: sadness: 0.02
On her third spaceflight in March 1994, Ivins flew with fellow Maggot Casper on STS-62, a 14-day microgravity research mission aboard Columbia.: neutral: 0.49
On her third spaceflight in March 1994, Ivins flew with fellow Maggot Casper on STS-62, a 14-day microgravity research mission aboard Columbia.: fear: 0.25
On her third spaceflight in March 1994, Ivins flew with fellow Maggot Casper on STS-62, a 14-day microgravity research mission aboard Columbia.: joy: 0.11
The nickname apparently originated with Shepherd, inspired during an early aircraft survival school session by the term U.S. Marines use for new recruits.: neutral: 0.94
The nickname apparently originated with Shepherd, inspired during an early aircraft survival school session by the term U.S. Marines use for new recruits.: disgust: 0.02
The nickname apparently originated with Shepherd, inspired during an early aircraft survival school session by the term U.S. Marines use for new recruits.: surprise: 0.02
For his third flight, he served as a mission specialist on STS-64, DiscoveryÆs 11-day mission in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: neutral: 0.40
For his third flight, he served as a mission specialist on STS-64, DiscoveryÆs 11-day mission in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: joy: 0.29
For his third flight, he served as a mission specialist on STS-64, DiscoveryÆs 11-day mission in September 1994, with the LIDAR in Space Technology Experiment as the primary payload.: fear: 0.22
During the nine-day flight aboard Atlantis, the crew deployed the fifth Tracking and Data Relay System (TDRS) satellite.: neutral: 0.92
During the nine-day flight aboard Atlantis, the crew deployed the fifth Tracking and Data Relay System (TDRS) satellite.: fear: 0.03
During the nine-day flight aboard Atlantis, the crew deployed the fifth Tracking and Data Relay System (TDRS) satellite.: surprise: 0.02
Over his four spaceflights, Lee spent 32 days 21 hours 52 minutes in space, and in the course of his four spacewalks, he spent 26 hours and one minute outside.: neutral: 0.88
Over his four spaceflights, Lee spent 32 days 21 hours 52 minutes in space, and in the course of his four spacewalks, he spent 26 hours and one minute outside.: surprise: 0.05
Over his four spaceflights, Lee spent 32 days 21 hours 52 minutes in space, and in the course of his four spacewalks, he spent 26 hours and one minute outside.: sadness: 0.04
During his expedition, he participated in a 5-hour 4-minute spacewalk.: neutral: 0.64
During his expedition, he participated in a 5-hour 4-minute spacewalk.: fear: 0.19
During his expedition, he participated in a 5-hour 4-minute spacewalk.: disgust: 0.07
She served as a mission specialist on her third flight, STS-61, the first servicing mission to the Hubble Space Telescope to correct its optics and perform other servicing tasks, with Thornton participating in two of the five spacewalks.: neutral: 0.87
She served as a mission specialist on her third flight, STS-61, the first servicing mission to the Hubble Space Telescope to correct its optics and perform other servicing tasks, with Thornton participating in two of the five spacewalks.: joy: 0.05
She served as a mission specialist on her third flight, STS-61, the first servicing mission to the Hubble Space Telescope to correct its optics and perform other servicing tasks, with Thornton participating in two of the five spacewalks.: fear: 0.03
Brown logged 10 days 9 hours 27 minutes in space on his two missions.: neutral: 0.90
Brown logged 10 days 9 hours 27 minutes in space on his two missions.: sadness: 0.04
Brown logged 10 days 9 hours 27 minutes in space on his two missions.: surprise: 0.03
On her second flight, Baker flew as a mission specialist on STS-50, the first U.S. Microgravity Laboratory Spacelab mission, the first to use the shuttleÆs Extended Duration Orbiter capabilities.: neutral: 0.67
On her second flight, Baker flew as a mission specialist on STS-50, the first U.S. Microgravity Laboratory Spacelab mission, the first to use the shuttleÆs Extended Duration Orbiter capabilities.: fear: 0.16
On her second flight, Baker flew as a mission specialist on STS-50, the first U.S. Microgravity Laboratory Spacelab mission, the first to use the shuttleÆs Extended Duration Orbiter capabilities.: surprise: 0.09
During the 10-day flight aboard Discovery in February 1997, Lee participated in three of the five spacewalks to install two new state-of-the-art instruments in the telescope and perform other servicing to extend its on-orbit lifetime.: neutral: 0.88
During the 10-day flight aboard Discovery in February 1997, Lee participated in three of the five spacewalks to install two new state-of-the-art instruments in the telescope and perform other servicing to extend its on-orbit lifetime.: joy: 0.04
During the 10-day flight aboard Discovery in February 1997, Lee participated in three of the five spacewalks to install two new state-of-the-art instruments in the telescope and perform other servicing to extend its on-orbit lifetime.: surprise: 0.03
Ohio-born Low, son of former NASA executive George M. Low, worked at NASAÆs Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, California, from 1980 until his selection as an astronaut.: neutral: 0.70
Ohio-born Low, son of former NASA executive George M. Low, worked at NASAÆs Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, California, from 1980 until his selection as an astronaut.: joy: 0.18
Ohio-born Low, son of former NASA executive George M. Low, worked at NASAÆs Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, California, from 1980 until his selection as an astronaut.: sadness: 0.05
The only Maggot to launch aboard a Russian Soyuz spacecraft, he flew aboard the station for 141 days between October 2000 and March 2001.: neutral: 0.89
The only Maggot to launch aboard a Russian Soyuz spacecraft, he flew aboard the station for 141 days between October 2000 and March 2001.: surprise: 0.06
The only Maggot to launch aboard a Russian Soyuz spacecraft, he flew aboard the station for 141 days between October 2000 and March 2001.: fear: 0.02
New York native and medical doctor Shulman, later using her married name Baker, began working at JSC in 1981 as a medical officer prior to her selection as an astronaut.: neutral: 0.46
New York native and medical doctor Shulman, later using her married name Baker, began working at JSC in 1981 as a medical officer prior to her selection as an astronaut.: joy: 0.37
New York native and medical doctor Shulman, later using her married name Baker, began working at JSC in 1981 as a medical officer prior to her selection as an astronaut.: fear: 0.07
He served as commander on his second mission, STS-56, in April 1993, the second Atmospheric Laboratory for Applications and Science (ATLAS) Earth observation mission aboard Discovery.: neutral: 0.84
He served as commander on his second mission, STS-56, in April 1993, the second Atmospheric Laboratory for Applications and Science (ATLAS) Earth observation mission aboard Discovery.: fear: 0.04
He served as commander on his second mission, STS-56, in April 1993, the second Atmospheric Laboratory for Applications and Science (ATLAS) Earth observation mission aboard Discovery.: joy: 0.04
As a group, they completed 51 flights and spending 706 days, or nearly two years, in space.: neutral: 0.77
As a group, they completed 51 flights and spending 706 days, or nearly two years, in space.: joy: 0.14
As a group, they completed 51 flights and spending 706 days, or nearly two years, in space.: surprise: 0.06
Wetherbee resumed his duties as JSC deputy center director in December 1997, remaining in that position until March 2000.: neutral: 0.89
Wetherbee resumed his duties as JSC deputy center director in December 1997, remaining in that position until March 2000.: joy: 0.04
Wetherbee resumed his duties as JSC deputy center director in December 1997, remaining in that position until March 2000.: sadness: 0.03
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: sadness: 0.61
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: fear: 0.23
The January 1986 Challenger accident resulted in the suspension of all flight and crew assignments.: anger: 0.08
29.375
